Brighter day friends to all who are
watching this video. I am
Deng Bautista, the trusted Sun Life
Financial advisor in Mayon.
I will show you one of the
common policies that
we present to our clients,
children or the elderly, young adults
or even very young people.
This policy is available to our son Maxilink
Prime. So what is the Maeling Prime?
This is a limited pay vul that is payable
for at least 10 years, with coverage
up to 88 years old. The
Death benefit face amount is always 200%
of what you will take. For example,
our minimum is 350,000, which will be divided into
2 periods. So what
our Ben Shars will get in case of death
is 700,000. Our eligibility issue
is zero. Up to 65 years old, the
minimum face amount
is 350,000. But you can
increase it by 500,000 million or more,
depending on your ability.  in the
budgets that you can set aside So
you can have excess premium allowed
here because this will go to your
savings Ah you can also
increase it Ah your life insurance
can be just a standalone life
insurance or You can
add Riders to it Like for example
the Accidental death
benefit accident dismemberment disable
disablement Or that then it can also be
a total disability benefit hospital
income benefit ah critical illnesses
benefit for children who are minors
who were taken by the owner for example the
elderly mother and father so they have a
what ah waver waver premium in
case of death of the owner of the insurance
so they also have a waver of premium If the
owner or
the one who took the insurance for the
minors becomes disabled So you can also
pay it monthly
quarterly annual or annual but in the first
payment in your first payment when
taking out the policy quarterly first Then
after that you can
make it
monthly there is also a loyalty
bonus called
ah at the end of the 10th Year of your
policy so this is the
Our sample calculation or quotation of
Sun Maeling Prime for a 24 year
old female who is a
non-smoker so this is her So our face
amount of
500,000 is what
we left for
our beneficiaries if we are first
so that is times 2 So that
means our beneficiary will get 1 million
so these are the additional
benefits the Riders called
additional riders are our additional payment
So the total disability
benefit the waver premium That is what happens if
the
insurance payer or the owner becomes totally disabled so
his payment is waved
he is the answer of Sunlife Of course upon evaluation
if the owner is really totally disabled
so this is the add
the Accidental death dismemberment
disablement
benefit
Okay so there we put
500,000 so that is what you will get so in case
you have an Accidental death
the cause of which is an accident Ah
so
500,000 plus your face amount of
500 is 1 million  so you will
get 1.5 I mean the beneficiary will get it
so there is also this
critical illness benefit so
this is what the owner will get.
In case he
has critical illnesses
so later what will we do with that we will not discuss
what the critical
illnesses are so if we put
500,000 then there is also this Rider that
you can also put a Rider for
hospital income
benefit so that whenever you are hospitalized
like for example 3 days that is
his eligibility we must have
at least 3 days to file so that we can have
a benefit of Php1,000 a day this is
the Accidental death dismemberment
and disability benefit so for example do
your benefit of
500,000
that is 500,000 for example if we
lose so the Life Is 100 per
That is 100% So it means There is a
percentage stated what we will
lose like if we lose
life so  100% plus our face amount
of 1 million so 1.5 we lose our
eyes but we are alive so of course
we can only get 500,000 because it is 100% so
both eyes that is both hands both feet 100%
and so on and so forth This is the
subcritical illness benefit so for the
critical illness benefit
ah for example today you paid
your first payment of your premium
it must have exceeded 90 days so
you will count 90 days after that
you can claim ah for
your critical illness So it
means less than 90 days in your
claim he will not be paid by ah
sunlight so that's what it says
below and we will not pay the
diagnosis within 90 days This is the
hospital income benefit called
ah that's what we get When we are
hospitalized Y one life insure is confined
hospital as a result of injury or
Sickness on the recommendation of I
physician as as inpatient you will
receive 1,000 as daily  so the
minimum should be 3 days so that
we can store it if we are
hospitalized and have been evaluated,
Dad should be in the intensive care unit so times 2,
so the 1,000 will become
2,000. So the same should be 3 days so
in 3 days we will get 6,000 so that's
the face amount of
500,000. You can see in the Basic plan
that our female is
21,800, we will pay 2315 critical illness
16 to 170 hospital income benefit
so our annual for a 24 year
old female who is non-smoker is
2,622 so her quarter is
7,000
156 that will be
our quarterly. So again, we should pay
the
quarterly first before we can get monthly
so it's really cheap especially when
you're young. Of course, it increases as we get older, that's how it is.
Of course, when you're young, it's cheaper so
as long as we're healthy, we should
get insurance there so it's easy.  It can
be paid off quickly and we
will pay less.
So like I said earlier,
it includes
investment, so this is what this
investment is about, so the investment is again
not guaranteed, it will not
automatically earn although it does have income,
but we cannot say
how much or how little,
because of course it depends on the stock
market, but after 10 years at 4%,
that's
4% in 10
years, it's possible that we will get
211,968, so that's what our insurance will earn,
of course, it's just a small amount,
because of course, only a portion of what
we pay for our life
insurance is invested here in Sun
Maxilink, so what we really focus on
is life insurance, so the
investment is secondary. So
at least we earn something, so
while you don't take that, it will still
automatically increase. So that's only 4%,
so it could be 8% or 10%
if the
stock market moves well, so it could
reach 287, of course, until
you take it in the 11th year.
It will still increase until 20 years so 732
is what he can get After 20 years if
you don't pay it first or if
he reaches maturity so This is
the death benefit of course of course
including our face amount for example
if and we lost So the 1 million
of course including our
ah income there in our investment so it
became 1.2 in the rider Like that
The
ah hospital
benefit then the critical illness
benefit a Sorry critical illness
benefit so after 10 years
we will still pay something so you noticed that
we finished paying our insurance on
the 10th year
that's why only on the 11th year
we still have it because it's a rider So what does
the Rider mean we will actually pay
it as an additional payment but
it will still be low Like for
example that 2000 that's all
he will pay annually for your
Riders critical illness and hospital
income benefit
of course if you don't
pay it he will no longer take
effect But it's still better for
us to pay it because of course while we
a  As we get older, we are more prone to
diseases, so let's really do this, at
least let's start now. Okay, so that's all, I
hope you liked
this policy, Sun Maxing Prime.
If you ever have any questions, you
can message me on my Facebook
account
below or can com so I can give
you
a sample calculation.